https://dotco.co.uk/privacy-policy/

© Dotco Limited 2020ask@dotco.co.ukLewes BN7 1RH UK
PrivacyOur privacy policy discloses how we gather, use and protect your data.Updated 12th March 2020 Dotco Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy discloses how we gather, use and protect your personal data.This Privacy Policy applies to personal data collected by Dotco through dotco.co.uk or by other means during the course of business.Who we areDotco Limited, St Anne’s Terrace, Lewes, BN7 1RH, UKAlso known as DOTask@dotco.co.uk www.dotco.ukWhy we collect dataDuring the course of carrying out our business and performing our services, Dotco collects personal data to conduct our business, provide our services, and meet our legal obligations.You may refuse to provide us with some or all of your personal data although that may limit the ways in which we can interact with you, including providing you with our services.Log filesWhen you access our website, your internet IP address is anonymised in our internet access logs (i.e., log files on server). We record the URLs of the websites and pages you visit, the times and dates of such visits, and information about the computer hardware and software used.This information may include browser type and version, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data, number of visits, websites from which you accessed our site (Referrer), and websites that are accessed by your system via our site.The processing of this data is necessary for the provision and the security of our website. We do not link these data to specific individuals. After the processing for the mentioned purposes, the data will be deleted.ContactOur contact form can be used to get in contact with us electronically. To handle your request it is necessary to provide us with a valid email address, and, in addition, we store your IP address and the time of your request to prevent any misuse of our contact forms. Alternatively, you may contact us via the e-mail address above. If you use one of these channels, the personal data transmitted will be stored automatically by Dotco as data controller to handle our contact with you.Unsolicited special categories of personal dataWe do not generally seek to collect special categories of personal data through this site.“Special categories of personal data” includes the various categories of personal information and data identified by privacy laws of United States, European and other jurisdictions as requiring special treatment, including in some circumstances the need to obtain explicit consent. These categories may include personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, genetic data, biometric data, data concerning health or data concerning sexual orientation.Therefore, we advise you not to provide any unsolicited sensitive personal data if you contact us. Dotco applies HTTPS or other appropriate technical and organizational measures to secure personal data transmitted over its website.CookiesDotco’s website uses cookies to save and retrieve information about your visit to our sites. Cookies are small files of software which save and retrieve information about your visit to a website or application. They reside in your internet browser to help remember your preferences and previous activity. You can find more information about cookies at www.allaboutcookies.org and www.youronlinechoices.euCookies currently used on our site identify you as an anonymized number. We and our partners (e.g. analytics providers) use cookies and log files to analyze trends, administer the website, track users movements around the website, and gather demographic information about our user base. We may receive anonymized reports based on the use of these technologies by our partners on an aggregated basis. We also use this data to provide the site’s content, ensure the functionality of our information technology systems, and to optimize our website. The data of log files will be stored separately from your other personal data.Users can control and refuse the use of cookies at the individual browser level. Cookies installed can be deleted. If you have visited our website in the past and would like to make changes to your cookie preferences, please first clear the cookies from your browser and then update your cookie preferences. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our website may be limited.When you visit our website, the following categories of cookies will be set in your browser:Strictly necessary cookiesThese cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around a site and use its features. Without these cookies services you have asked for cannot be provided.Performance cookiesThese cookies collect information so that we can analyse how our visitors use our site. These cookies do not collect information that identifies you. All information these cookies collect is anonymous and is only used to improve how our site works.Targeting cookiesIn order to keep our website services relevant, easy to use and up-to-date, we use web analytics services to help us understand how people use the site.Cookies allow web analytics services to recognise your browser or device and, for example, identify whether you have visited our website before, what you have previously viewed or clicked on, and how you found us. The information is anonymous and only used for statistical purposes, and it helps us to analyse patterns of user activity and to develop a better user experience.Third Party ApplicationsWe will respect and protect your privacy as set out in this Privacy Policy. We will share your personal data with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy – and do not and will not sell your personal data.Dotco shares your personal data with third parties, in particular no-Dotco parties, only with your express consent or under another lawful basis for processing under the applicable law.Categories of non-Dotco parties with which we share your personal data include vendors such as host and cloud service providers and sub-contractors involved in the fulfilment of our contractual obligations towards our clients.Google AnalyticsOur website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google, Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA, www.google.com (“Google Analytics” or “Google”). Google Analytics employs cookies that are stored to your computer in order to facilitate an analysis of your use of the site. The information generated by these cookies, such as time, place and frequency of your visits to our site, including your IP address, is transmitted to Google’s location in the US and stored there.In using Google Analytics our website anonymises your IP address. In doing so, Google abbreviates and thereby anonymises your IP address before transferring it from EU/EEA member states. Google uses this information to analyze your use of our site, to compile reports for us on internet activity and to provide other services relating to our website.Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law or where such third parties process this data on Google’s behalf. Google states that it will in never associate your IP address with other data held by Google. You can prevent cookies from being installed by adjusting the settings on your browser software accordingly as noted elsewhere in this Privacy Policy. You should be aware, however, that by doing so you may not be able to make full use of all the functions of our website.Google Analytics also offers a deactivation add-on for most current browsers that provides you with more control over what data Google can collect on websites you access. The add-on tells the JavaScript (ga.js) used by Google Analytics not to transmit any information about website visits to Google Analytics. However, the browser deactivation add-on offered by Google Analytics does not prevent information from being transmitted to us or to other web analysis services we may engage.Google Analytics also uses electronic images known as web beacons (sometimes called single pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used.You can find additional information on how to install the browser add-on referenced above at the following link: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.For the cases in which personal data is transferred to the US, Google has self-certified pursuant to the EU-US Privacy Shield (https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework).Deletion and Term of StorageDotco processes and stores your personal data only for the time necessary to achieve the stated purpose (unless otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy) and as permitted under the applicable laws or regulations.As soon as the purpose for data storage is achieved, or the appropriate term of storage provided for by any applicable laws or regulations expires, your personal data will be deleted consistent with this and any other applicable Dotco policies (e.g., document retention and/or records management policy) unless your personal data are required for the formation of or performance under a contract.Your rights as data subjectYou have the following rights:Right of accessIn principle, you have the right to receive information on the points mentioned in Art. 15 GDPR. You also have the right to request a copy of your personal data in accordance with Art. 15 (3) GDPR.Right to rectification or erasureYou have the right to have incorrect personal data corrected. In addition, you have the right to demand that your personal data is deleted if further processing is no longer necessary, if processing is unlawful or if you have withdrawn your consent.Right to restriction of processingIf the conditions in Art. 18 GDPR are met, you have the right to have the processing of your personal data restricted, i.e. to prevent further processing for the time being.Right to objectIf the processing of your personal data is based on Art. 6 (1)e or f GDPR, you have the right to object to the processing if the further requirements of Art. 21 GDPR are met.Right to data portabilityWithin the limits of Art. 20 GDPR, you have the right to receive your personal data in a machine-readable format in order to forward it or have it forwarded to another controller.You can require this by sending us an email at ask@dotco.co.ukWithout prejudice to any other administrative or judicial remedy, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the location of your habitual residence, place of work or place of the alleged infringement if you consider that the processing of personal data relating to you infringes the applicable data protection laws and regulations.Changes to the PolicyThis Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time and will note the date of any updates.  In the event of any material and significant changes we will endeavor to provide a more prominent notice of the changes to this Privacy Policy.
Search
© Dotco Limited 2020 ask@dotco.co.uk  Lewes BN7 1RH UK
Our website uses cookies. OK Cookie settings Privacy Privacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
